Contact

stonew061@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/wendy-stoneb9618659 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Patient Safety

Surgery

Ambulatory Care

Certifications

Cardiac Surgery (Adult) (CSC) Critical Care Registered Nurse (Adult) (CCRN-A)

Wendy Stone

BSN, RN, CCRN-CSC

Tyler, Texas

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working as a team member in the hospital & health care industry. Specializing in immediate post operative recovery of CABG and open heart patients. Strong healthcare services professional with supervisory experience in charge nurse role. Experience with Impella devices, IABP, CRRT, targeted temperature management, EKOS therapy, and post cardiac arrest care.

Experience

Travel Nurse Across America Registered Nurse January 2020 - Present (6 months)

CHRISTUS Trinity Mother Frances Health System CVICU RN

May 2014 - Present (6 years 2 months)

Tyler, Texas

East Texas Medical Center

2 years 4 months

RN

May 2013 - December 2014 (1 year 8 months)

PRN in Surgery. Working as a circulator, recovery nurse, and in Ambulatory Care.

LVN

September 2012 - May 2013 (9 months)

Athens

Kemp Care Center

LVN

January 2012 - October 2012 (10 months)

Education

The University of Texas at Arlington
BSN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2018 - 2019)

Trinity Valley Community College
Associate of Science (AS), Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2012 - 2013)

Trinity Valley Community College Vocational Nursing Certificate · (2011 - 2011)